enggwave.com 2012-05-18

# Privacy Policy - Engineering Wave

## **_Privacy Policy:_**

**_Terms of Use:_**  
While we have made every effort to provide accurate and meaningful information on our website, we cannot guarantee its accuracy. We are not responsible for any actions that you perform based on the content of this site or damages that are a direct or indirect result of its use.

**_What information do we collect?_**  
We collect information from you when you respond to a survey, fill out a form or comment.   
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

 ** _What do we use your information for?_  **  
 Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

1\.  To personalize your experience  
     (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

2\.  To improve our website  
    (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

3\.  To send periodic emails The email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information   
     and updates pertaining to your order. If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include    
     company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

 ** _Do we use cookies?_  **  
Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.   
Third parties may be placing and reading cookies on your browser, or using web beacons to collect information, in the course of ads being served on this website. To prevent cookies being placed on your computers please disable them in your browser’s options. Consult your web browser’s documentation for more information.

 ** _Do we disclose any information to outside parties?_  **  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

 ** _Third party links_**    
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 ** _Your Consent  _**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

 ** _Advertisers_**  
We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and are collected by the ad companies, and we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google Adsense, etc. Please check their websites for respective privacy policies. 

 ** _Changes to our Privacy Policy_**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
